<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wilderness Bushcamp</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/</link><description>Recent content on Wilderness Bushcamp</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aloe Studio</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-studio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-studio/</guid><description>This cosy studio apartment is located near the reception area so is the perfect choice for someone who wants to have convenient access and be a little less “in the bush” but still be able to enjoy a private deck with far reaching ocean views.</description></item><item><title>Aloe Suite</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-suite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-suite/</guid><description>A private gateway leads to this spacious and comfortable self-catering suite, which is attached to the main house but enjoys total privacy.</description></item><item><title>Hideaway Cottage</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/hideaway-cottage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/hideaway-cottage/</guid><description>Discreetly located at the end of a wooden walkway and hidden amongst dense bush, this is the perfect choice for those who don’t want to be disturbed.</description></item><item><title>Sunrise Ridge</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/sunrise-ridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/sunrise-ridge/</guid><description>A wooden boardwalk leads down to this cosy wooden cabin, built for two. Step out of bed and onto your deck to watch the sun rise over the lagoon and the ocean</description></item><item><title>Loerie Cabin</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/loerie-cabin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/loerie-cabin/</guid><description>This cosy log cabin welcomed its first guests in 1995 and is still one of our favourites. It offers rustic accommodation for families or groups of friends – and has a private deck with uninterrupted views of the ocean</description></item><item><title>Lagoon View</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/lagoon-view/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/lagoon-view/</guid><description>This is one of our most popular cabins, with a private deck that offers glorious views of Wilderness lagoon and the ocean. There’s no better place to watch the sun rise while you enjoy your early morning cup of coffee…</description></item><item><title>Forest Rise</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/forest-rise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/forest-rise/</guid><description>This newly built 2-bedroom cottage is situated on the uppermost section of the hill and is perfect for families. The slide from the deck onto the garden is designed for the kids but is also fun for the young at heart.</description></item><item><title>Bird Haven</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/bird-haven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/bird-haven/</guid><description>This beautifully appointed cottage sits in an area that was once the uppermost section of a bird sanctuary. The surrounding fynbos and vegetation still teems with birdlife, so bring your binoculars…</description></item><item><title>Featured on wantedonline.co.za - May 2020</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/wanted-online-coza-may-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/wanted-online-coza-may-2020/</guid><description>In the midst of the lockdown we were honoured to receive a special mention from Wesgro CEO, Tim Harris, in an interview for Business Day’s Wanted Online…</description></item><item><title>Escapes Magazine - April 2020</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/escapes-magazine-april-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/escapes-magazine-april-2020/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Featured on visitgeorge.co.za - July 2020</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/visit-george-coza-feb-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/visit-george-coza-feb-2020/</guid><description>In July, our Forest Rise cabin was highlighted by George Tourism as an ideal getaway for families wanting a break away after the lockdown&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Country Life Magazine - May 2019</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/country-life-may-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/country-life-may-2019/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/contact-us/</guid><description>Contact Us C | 078 419 2021 Send us an Email Physical Address Wilderness Bushcamp Beacon Road Wilderness Postal Address PO Box 1042 6530 George South Africa Directions Wilderness is located just off the N2, approximately 15km from George.
Once you turn off the N2 into Wilderness Village please take an immediate left turn onto Beacon Road.
Follow Beacon Road past the Milkwood Village and past the Kwik Spar.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/covid-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/covid-19/</guid><description>Wilderness Bushcamp will be following strict health and safety protocol to ensure the safety of guests and staff during all levels of the Covid19 lockdown:
Mandatory face masks for staff at all times and for guests in public areas Contactless check-in and check-out. All paperwork will be completed via email and check-in information will be sent by email and WhatsApp 24-hour vacancy between guests Keys will be disinfected prior to being handed over or left in the key safe Hand sanitiser is available on arrival and departure and in public areas The indoor reception area will remain closed during lockdown.</description></item><item><title>Rates and Bookings</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/rates-and-bookings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/rates-and-bookings/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Lapa</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/the-lapa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/the-lapa/</guid><description>Each unit has its own private deck with outdoor dining area, but not all units are equipped with a braai, so guests are welcome to make use of the communal lapa area during their stay…
The Lapa is close to Loerie Cabin, Hideaway Cottage and Aloe Studio, but is available for all guests to use and enjoy *
If a group is interested in booking out the whole Bushcamp then it’s possible to secure exclusive use of The Lapa so that they can gather there to enjoy meals together.</description></item><item><title>Things to do</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/things-to-do/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/things-to-do/</guid><description>Wilderness is a truly unique place. This garden of Eden is blessed with ocean, mountains, forests and rivers that converge to create a natural paradise just waiting to be explored.
There are hiking trails and biking tracks, forest walks and riverside meanders, fishing spots, mountains to climb, rock pools to explore, world famous paragliding conditions and the endless rolling of the ocean, which beckons you to kick off your shoes and set off along the pristine beaches that stretch as far as the eye can see…</description></item><item><title>Wildside Magazine - Summer 2017</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/wildside-magazine-summer-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/media/wildside-magazine-summer-2017/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>