<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accommodation on Wilderness Bushcamp</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/</link><description>Recent content in Accommodation on Wilderness Bushcamp</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aloe Studio</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-studio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-studio/</guid><description>This cosy studio apartment is located near the main house so is the perfect choice for someone who wants to have convenient access and be a little less “in the bush” but still be able to enjoy a private deck with far reaching ocean views.</description></item><item><title>Aloe Suite</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-suite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/aloe-heights/aloe-suite/</guid><description>A private gateway leads to this spacious and comfortable self-catering suite, which is attached to the main house but enjoys total privacy.</description></item><item><title>Hideaway Cottage</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/hideaway-cottage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/hideaway-cottage/</guid><description>Discreetly located at the end of a wooden walkway and hidden amongst dense bush, this is the perfect choice for those who don’t want to be disturbed.</description></item><item><title>Sunrise Ridge</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/sunrise-ridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/sunrise-ridge/</guid><description>A wooden boardwalk leads down to this cosy wooden cabin, built for two. Step out of bed and onto your deck to watch the sun rise over the lagoon and the ocean</description></item><item><title>Loerie Cabin</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/loerie-cabin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/loerie-cabin/</guid><description>This cosy log cabin welcomed its first guests in 1995 and is still one of our favourites. It offers rustic accommodation for families or groups of friends – and has a private deck with uninterrupted views of the ocean</description></item><item><title>Lagoon View</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/lagoon-view/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/lagoon-view/</guid><description>This is one of our most popular cabins, with a private deck that offers glorious views of Wilderness lagoon and the ocean. There’s no better place to watch the sun rise while you enjoy your early morning cup of coffee…</description></item><item><title>Forest Rise</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/forest-rise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/forest-rise/</guid><description>This newly built 2-bedroom cottage is situated on the uppermost section of the hill and is perfect for families. The slide from the deck onto the garden is designed for the kids but is also fun for the young at heart.</description></item><item><title>Bird Haven</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/bird-haven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/accommodation/bushcamp/bird-haven/</guid><description>This beautifully appointed cottage sits in an area that was once the uppermost section of a bird sanctuary. The surrounding fynbos and vegetation still teems with birdlife, so bring your binoculars…</description></item><item><title>The Lapa</title><link>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/the-lapa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wildernessbushcamp.co.za/the-lapa/</guid><description>Each unit has its own private deck with outdoor dining area, but not all units are equipped with a braai, so guests are welcome to make use of the communal lapa area during their stay…
The Lapa is close to Loerie Cabin, Hideaway Cottage and Aloe Studio, but is available for all guests to use and enjoy *
If a group is interested in booking out the whole Bushcamp then it’s possible to secure exclusive use of The Lapa so that they can gather there to enjoy meals together.</description></item></channel></rss>